adikteev.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy – Adikteev

The ADIKTEEV Privacy Policy was updated on February 06th, 2018.

Your personal data is important to Adikteev ( **“ADIKTEEV** “ or **“We** “). So We have developed a privacy policy ( **“Privacy Policy** “) that explains how We use, disclose, transfer and store your personal data that we collect from (i) our website [www.adikteev.com](http://www.adikteev.com/) (the **“** **Website”** ), (ii) the operation of our advertising services that We provide to advertisers that market, offer and/or operate websites or applications that you may access and (iii) business partner websites that are member of our network (the “ **Services”** ). Please take a moment to read the Privacy Policy and email us ([legal@adikteev.com](mailto:legal@adikteev.com)) if you have any questions.

> 1\. How We collect data

**1.1** Regarding ADIKTEEV’s customers, ADIKTEEV collects information about you from:

  * your use of the Website;
  * your subscription to ADIKTEEV’s Newsletter;
  * email’s you send to ADIKTEEV; and
  * your access to the Website backoffice, as applicable.

**1.2** Regarding end-users, ADIKTEEV collects information about you from:

  * directly from your use of the Services ( _e.g._ when you visit an advertiser’s website, browse information and/or buy an item of the said website);
  * directly from your devices; and
  * indirectly from third party data providers such as Exelate and Netacuity
  * indirectly from tracking partners such as Appsalar, Tune, Adjust, Kochava, Appsflyer

> 2\. Categories of data We collect

**2.1** Regarding ADIKTEEV’s customers, the categories of data that ADIKTEEV collects from you include :

  * identification information (e.g. name, surname, email address, telephone number);
  * professional life (e.g. job position, company); and
  * connection data ( _e.g._ Â login credentials access, date and time access to the Website and/or Website backoffice);

**2.2** Regarding end-users, the categories of data that ADIKTEEV collects directly and indirectly from you include :

  * data relating to your personal life ( _e.g_. tastes derived from your browsing history); and
  * connection data ( _e.g._ the publisher / URL accessed, Internet protocol address, device information and event information, date and time access to a business partner website, member of ADIKTEEV’s network).

> 3\. Use of cookies and similar technologies

ADIKTEEV and its business partners use various technologies to collect and store information relating to end-user’s use of desktop and mobile web services. This section does not apply to ADIKTEEV services relating to mobile application.

When you visit a website, and this may include using cookies or similar technologies to identify your browser and/or device. Cookies are text files containing a string of characters which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website and enable a website to recognize your device on each subsequent visit. This section does not apply to ADIKTEEV activities on applications.

**3.1 Strictly necessary cookies**

This category of cookies are necessary to enable you to move around the Website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Website.

You may deactivate these cookies using your browser settings ( _e.g._ Â for web browsers : [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647), [Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411) and [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences); and for mobile platforms: [iOS](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT205223), [Android](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922) and [Windows Phone](https://choice.microsoft.com/en-US/opt-out)). ADIKTEEV informs you that their deactivation may lead to a drop in performance of the Website.

**3.2 Functionality cookies  
**

This category of cookies allows ADIKTEEV to remember the choices you have made while visiting the Website such as, where applicable, you user name, passwords and other preferences.

You may deactivate these cookies by following the instructions provided at <https://www.adikteev.com/cookies>. ADIKTEEV informs you that their deactivation may lead to a drop in performance of the Website.

**3.3. Performance cookies**

This category of cookies only collect information about the use of the Website for the benefit of ADIKTEEV in order to manage the performance and design of the Website.

You may deactivate these cookies by following the instructions provided at <https://www.adikteev.com/cookies>. ADIKTEEV informs you that their deactivation may lead to a drop in performance of the Website.

**3.4 Profiling and targeting and advertising cookies**

This category of cookies are used as part of an advertising network and enables ADIKTEEV to collect information when you visit an advertiser’s website and/or a business partner website. Targeting and advertising cookies also enable ADIKTEEV to distinguish your browsing habits; remember the websites you have visited; interactions and actions you have performed while visiting a website ( _e.g._ ADIKTEEV attributes a click or an impression on an advertisement to a specific user), deliver adverts, on behalf of advertisers, more relevant to you, limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaigns.

You may deactivate these cookies by following the instructions provided at <https://www.adikteev.com/cookies>. ADIKTEEV informs you that their deactivation may lead to a drop in performance of the Services.

> 4\. How We use data

**4.1 Legal basis of the personal data processing**

The legal basis for the processing of personal data by ADIKTEEV relies:

  * regarding ADIKTEEV’s customers, on the agreement entered into between the customer and ADIKTEEV;
  * regarding end-users, the legitimate interest of ADIKTEEV to deliver interest based advertisings only so as to deliver more relevant adverts and limit the number of times an advert is displayed to you, provided that ADIKTEEV has offered you the technical measures to oppose such processing.

**4.2 Purposes of the personal data processing**

4.1.1 Regarding ADIKTEEV’s customers, ADIKTEEV uses your information and personal data that it collects and/or is provided with to:

  * provide you, where applicable, access to our business platform backoffice in the Website;
  * manage our customer relationship;
  * deliver interest-based advertising to users;
  * track the advertising;
  * train, optimize and adjust our advertising tools and Services;
  * evaluate and improve the Website and the Services; and
  * measure and analyze the performance of advertiser’s advertising campaigns to provide them with reports and assist them in optimizing metrics.

4.1.2 Regarding end-users, ADIKTEEV uses your information and personal data that it collects and/or is provided with to:

  * provide you information about product, services, promotions, contests, or other activities or offerings based on your interests; and
  * deliver interest-based advertising.

ADIKTEEV uses data provided by its third-party data providers to enrich your information for the above mentioned purposes.

> 5\. Data retention

**5.1 Regarding ADIKTEEV’s customers**

Regarding ADIKTEEV’s customers, ADIKTEEV will use and retain your personal data for a period of time not exceeding the greater of:

  * where applicable, the duration of your account;
  * the duration of the processing of your requests;
  * the duration of the advertising campaigns;
  * the applicable duration of statute of limitations.

**5.2 Regarding end-users**

Regarding end-users, ADIKTEEV will use and retain your personal data for a period of time not exceeding the greater of:

  * the delivery of interest-based advertising campaigns implemented on behalf of advertisers;
  * three years as from the term of the commercial relationship ( _e.g_. a purchase on a website and/or application of Adikteev’s customers);
  * three years as from the data collection; and
  * the applicable duration of statute of limitations.

ADIKTEEV will use the cookies you have accepted for a period of time not exceeding thirteen (13) months as from the date of their implementation.

> 6\. Data recipients

ADIKTEEV may need to disclose your personal data to:

  * enforce and protect our rights and properties; and
  * respond to and/or comply with applicable regulations, law, court order and/or any other legal obligation.

**6.1** Regarding ADIKTEEV’s customers, ADIKTEEV may share your personal data with its :

  * authorized members of personnel; and
  * third party processors.

**6.2** Regarding end-users, ADIKTEEV may share your information and personal data with its:

  * authorized members of personnel; and
  * third party processors.

> 7\. User rights

Regarding end-users, please note that your personal data is used for profiling and targeting advertising purposes.

Where applicable, both the end-users and ADIKTEEV’s customers as data subjects may access, rectify, delete their personal data, limit the processing of personal data and, for legitimate reasons, oppose to the processing of their personal data. Both end-users and ADIKTEEV’s customers can also contact ADIKTEEV to define the instructions for the processing of their personal data after their death. Please also note that ADIKTEEV’s customers may exercise their right to data portability.

Both the end-users and ADIKTEEV’s customers have the right to, at any time, as well as to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

In case of any difficulty with the exercise of any of the rights here above mentioned, do not hesitate to email us at [legal@adikteev.com](mailto:legal@adikteev.com) .

> 8\. Security measures

We implement number of security measures appropriate to ensure the security of your information and, notably, prevent any alteration, corruption and any unauthorized access by any third party.

> 9\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

ADIKTEEV may change from time to time the terms of the Privacy Policy and endeavors to notify you any change and/or update by posting the latest version of the Privacy Policy on this page and indicating the updated revision date.

> 10\. Contact ADIKTEEV

Any question relating to personal data processing by ADIKTEEV and/or this Privacy Policy, please email us at [legal@adikteev.com](mailto:legal@adikteev.com) .
